Guide to the Actors' Equity Association Records WAG.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Contracts/Agreements/Codes
  - Subseries F: Guest Artist
    - Oregon, Ohio: Excalibur Productions at Fassett Auditorium, 1974 (Box 231, Folder 23)
    - Oriskany, New York: Upstate Lyric Theater, 1974 (Box 231, Folder 24)
    - Orlando, Florida: Central Florida Civic Theatre, 1973 (Box 231, Folder 25)
    - Pensacola, Florida: Pensacola Junior College, 1975-1976 (Box 231, Folder 26)
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania: Annenberg Center at the University of Pennsylvania, 1975-1976 (Box 231, Folder 27)
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania: Temple University Randall Lab Theatre, 1971 (Box 231, Folder 28)
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania: Temple University Stage Three/Theatre Three, 1974, 1976 (Box 231, Folder 29)
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania: Temple University Tomlinson Theatre, 1977 (Box 231, Folder 30)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh City Players, 1976 (Box 231, Folder 31)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh Playhouse (Box 231, Folder 31A)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: Vanguard Theatre formerly Vanguard Theatre Project, Pittsburgh Playhouse School of the Theatre, 1965-1972 (Box 231, Folder 32)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: Point Park College, 1976 (Box 231, Folder 33)
    - Poland, Maine: Tripp Lake Camp, 1975-1976 (Box 231, Folder 34)
    - Port Jefferson, New York: Slavic Cultural Center, 1975-1976 (Box 231, Folder 35)
    - Port Jervis, New York: Port Jervis Public School, 1977 (Box 231, Folder 36)
    - Purchase, New York: State University of New York College at Purchase, 1976-1977 (Box 231, Folder 37)
    - Reading, Pennsylvania: Pennsylvania State University, The Berks Campus, 1977 (Box 231, Folder 38)
    - Richmond, Virginia: Virginia Museum Theatre (Actor-Teacher and Guest Artist Contracts), 1968-1972 (Box 231, Folder 39)
    - Ridgebury, New York: New Country Theatre, 1971 (Box 231, Folder 40)
    - River Falls, Wisconsin: University of Wisconsin, 1973 (Box 231, Folder 41)
    - Roanoke, Virginia: Mill Mountain Playhouse, 1973-1974, 1977 (Box 231, Folder 42)
    - Rochester, New York: Eastman School of Music, University of Rochester, 1976 (Box 231, Folder 43)
    - Rochester, New York: Strassenburgh Planetarium, 1974 (Box 231, Folder 44)
    - Rockport, Massachusetts: Cape Ann Playhouse, 1974 (Box 231, Folder 45)
    - Rockville, Maryland: Harlequin Dinner Theatre (Dinner Theatre and Guest Artist Contracts), 1974-1975, 1977 (Box 231, Folder 46)
    - St. Louis, Missouri: The Repertory Theatre, Loretto Hilton, 1971 (Box 231, Folder 47)
    - St. Peter, Minnesota: Gustavus Adolphus College, 1973 (Box 231, Folder 48)
    - St. Petersburg, Florida: St. Petersburg Junior College, 1977 (Box 231, Folder 49)
    - Salem, Massachusetts: Salem State Theatre, 1976-1977 (Box 231, Folder 50)
    - Saratoga Springs, New York: Skidmore College, 1977 (Box 231, Folder 51)
    - Schenectady, New York: Union College, 1977 (Box 231, Folder 52)
    - Selinsgrove, Pennsylvania: Susquehanna University, 1976 (Box 231, Folder 53)
    - Shamokin Dam, Pennsylvania: Brookside Playhouse, 1972 (Box 231, Folder 54)
    - Shamokin Dam, Pennsylvania: Valley Players, 1974 (Box 231, Folder 55)
    - Shreveport, Louisiana: Prytania Energy Theatre, The Little Theatre, 1974 (Box 231, Folder 56)
    - Slate Hill, New York: Minisink Valley Central School, 1974 (Box 231, Folder 57)
    - South Huntington, New York: Holy Family Diocesan High School, 1975 (Box 231, Folder 58)
    - Staten Island, New York: Wagner College, 1974 (Box 231, Folder 59)
    - Staten Island, New York: Staten Island Community College, 1970 (Box 231, Folder 60)
    - Stony Brook, New York: State University of New York at Stony Brook, 1965, 1972 (Box 231, Folder 61)
    - Sweet Briar, Virginia: Sweet Briar College, 1971 (Box 231, Folder 62)
    - Syracuse, New York: Salt City Playhouse, 1972-1973 (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Syracuse, New York: University Regent Theatre, Syracuse Repertory Theatre at Syracuse University, 1972-1973, 1976 (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - Tampa, Florida: Ensemble Theatre Company, 1976 (Box 232, Folder 3)
    - Tampa, Florida: Tampa Community Theatre, 1977 (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - Tampa, Florida: University of South Florida (Actor-Teacher and Guest Artist Contracts), 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - Tarrytown, New York: Marymount College, 1969-1974 (Box 232, Folder 6)
    - Tarrytown, New York: Marymount College, 1975-1978 (Box 232, Folder 7)
    - Toledo, Ohio: Lynro Productions at the State Theatre, 1967 (Box 232, Folder 8)
    - Toledo, Ohio: Toledo Repertoire Theatre, 1971 (Box 232, Folder 9)
    - University Park, Pennsylvania: Pennsylvania State University, 1970 (Box 232, Folder 10)
    - University Park, Pennsylvania: Pennsylvania State University, 1973-1974 (Box 232, Folder 11)
    - University Park, Pennsylvania: Pennsylvania State University, 1975-1976 (Box 232, Folder 12)
    - Upper Montclair, New Jersey: Montclair Operetta Club, 1969-1974 (Box 232, Folder 13)
    - Upper Montclair, New Jersey: Montclair Operetta Club, 1975-1979 (Box 232, Folder 14)
    - Urbana, Illinois: The University Theatre at the University of Illinois, 1969-1971, 1975 (Box 232, Folder 15)
    - Venice, Florida: Venice Little Theatre, 1977-1978 (Box 232, Folder 16)
    - Vienna, Virginia: Wolf Trap Farm Park for the Performing Arts, 1970-1972 (Box 232, Folder 17)
    - Vienna, Virginia: Wolf Trap Farm Park for the Performing Arts, 1973-1975 (Box 232, Folder 18)
    - Washington, D.C.: American Players Theatre, 1977 (Box 232, Folder 19)
    - Washington, D.C.: American Theatre Association, 1974-1977 (Box 232, Folder 20)
    - Washington, D.C.: American University, 1976 (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Washington, D.C.: Catholic University, 1977 (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Washington, D.C.: Folger Theatre, 1970-1974 (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Washington, D.C.: Folger Theatre (Guest Artist and Actor/Teacher Contracts), 1975-1976 (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Washington, D.C.: Strolling Troubadours in National Parks, 1975-1976 (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Washington, D.C.: Washington Cathedral, 1972 (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Waterville, Maine: Colby College, 1977 (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - Waterville, Maine: Waterville Community Theatre, 1976 (Box 233, Folder 8)
    - Waterville, Maine: Waterville Opera House, 1976 (Box 233, Folder 9)
    - Westfield, Massachusetts: Westfield State College, 1976 (Box 233, Folder 10)
    - Westtown, Pennsylvania: The Philadelphia Company, Westtown School, 1975 (Box 233, Folder 11)
    - Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania: Wilkes College, 1976 (Box 233, Folder 12)
    - Wilmington, Ohio: Wilmington College, 1975 (Box 233, Folder 13)
    - Winston-Salem, North Carolina: The Little Theatre, 1975-1976 (Box 233, Folder 14)
    - Winston-Salem, North Carolina: North Carolina School of the Arts, 1973 (Box 233, Folder 15)
    - Winter Park, Florida: Annie Russell Summer Theatre at Rollins College, 1968-1977 (Box 233, Folder 16)
  - Subseries G: Actor/Teacher [to become U/RTA; University/Resident Theatre Association Contract]
    - Anniston. Alabama: Alabama Shakespeare Festival, 1977, 1979 (Box 233, Folder 17)
    - Baltimore, Maryland: Towson State University (Actor/Teacher, Guest Artist and U/RTA Contracts), 1969, 1973-1975, 1977 (Box 233, Folder 18)
    - Boston, Massachusetts: Massachusetts Arts and Humanities Foundation, 1974 (Box 233, Folder 19)
    - Cambridge, Massachusetts: Loeb Drama Center at Harvard University, 1977 (Box 233, Folder 20)
    - Fayetteville, North Carolina: Fayetteville City Schools, 1976-1977 (Box 233, Folder 21)
    - Friendship, Maryland: Professional Resources Organization, 1977 (Box 233, Folder 22)
    - Hartford, Connecticut: Trinity College, 1977-1978 (Box 233, Folder 23)
    - Kansas City, Missouri: University of Missouri-Kansas City, 1974 (Box 233, Folder 24)
    - Keuka Park, New York: Keuka College Summer Theatre, 1977 (Box 233, Folder 25)
    - Kingston, Rhode Island: University of Rhode Island Festival of the Arts, 1977 (Box 233, Folder 26)
    - Louisville, Kentucky: Louisville Children's Theatre, 1975 (Box 233, Folder 27)
    - McHenry, Maryland: Garrett Community College, 1974 (Box 233, Folder 28)
    - Memphis, Tennessee: Lausanne School-Front Street Musical Theatre, 1972 (Box 233, Folder 29)
    - Meridian, Mississippi: Meridian Junior College, 1975 (Box 233, Folder 30)
    - Moylan, Pennsylvania: Hedgerow Theatre (Actor/Teacher and Guest Artist Contracts), 1969, 1971, 1973-1975 (Box 233, Folder 31)
    - New Haven, Connecticut: Southern Connecticut State College, 1975-1977 (Box 233, Folder 32)
    - New York, New York: Four Winds Theatre, 1968-1969, 1971, 1974-1976 (Box 233, Folder 33)
    - New York, New York: Theatre of the Riverside Church, 1973-1974 (Box 233, Folder 34)
    - Newport, Rhode Island: The Newport School, 1973 (Box 233, Folder 35)
    - Niceville, Florida: Okaloosa-Walton Junior College, 1973 (Box 233, Folder 36)
    - Oak Bluffs, Massachusetts: Vineyard Players Foundation, 1972-1975 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania: La Salle College, 1974 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: First Presbyterian Church, 1973 (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: Point Park College, 1970-1971, 1974 (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania: Pittsburgh Playhouse, 1970-1971 (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - Princeton, New Jersey: McCarter Theatre, 1977 (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Princeton, New Jersey: Princeton University, 1977-1979 (Box 234, Folder 7)
    - Princeton, New Jersey: Summer Intime at Hamilton Murray Theater, 1974-1975 (Box 234, Folder 8)
    - Putney, Vermont: Vermont School of the Arts at Windham College (Actor/Teacher and Guest Artist Contracts), 1973-1977 (Box 234, Folder 9)
    - Rochester, New York: Genesee Valley Arts Foundation (GEVA), 1972-1974 (Box 234, Folder 10)
    - Rochester, New York: National Technical Institute of the Deaf, 1975 (Box 234, Folder 11)
    - Santa Maria, California: Pacific Conservatory of the Performing Arts (PCPA), 1975 (Box 234, Folder 12)
    - Sea Cliff, New York: Nassau Stage Company, 1974 (Box 234, Folder 13)
    - Stony Brook, New York: State University of New York (SUNY) as Stony Brook (Actor/Teacher), 1975-1976 (Box 234, Folder 14)
    - Stony Brook, New York: State University of New York (SUNY) as Stony Brook (U/RTA), 1977 (Box 234, Folder 15)
    - University Park, Pennsylvania: Pennsylvania State Festival Theatre, 1977 (Box 234, Folder 16)
    - Wayne, New Jersey: William Patterson College, 1975-1976 (Box 234, Folder 17)
    - Williamsport, Pennsylvania: Lycoming College, 1973 (Box 234, Folder 18)
  - Subseries H: Special Production Contract [also referred to/bonded as "Dramatic/Musical, Special Contract"]
    - AC-DC: New York "closed", Mar 14, 1971 (Box 234, Folder 19)
    - Acife & Pendabis[ Going Thru Changes and The Past is the Past] New York "closed" [also On Being Hit"closed" Dec 8, 1973], Feb 23, 1974 (Box 234, Folder 20)
    - Action: New York "closed", May 3, 1975 (Box 234, Folder 21)
    - All Night Strut: Washington, D.C. "closed", Jul 10, 1977 (Box 234, Folder 22)
    - American Place Theatre: correspondence and materials, 1969-1973 (Box 234, Folder 23)
    - And Still I Rise: Washington, D.C., 1977 (Box 234, Folder 24)
    - Anna Christie: Cleveland, Ohio "closed", Jun 12, 1977 (Box 234, Folder 25)
    - Anniversary Waltz: Los Angeles "closed" [played San Francisco and may have toured—could be Production Contract], Feb 23, 1957 (Box 234, Folder 26)
    - Autumn's Here: New York "closed", Dec 31, 1966 (Box 234, Folder 27)
    - Baba Goya: New York "closed", Jun 2, 1973 (Box 234, Folder 28)
    - Back, Bog, Beast, Bait: New York "closed", Jun 5, 1971 (Box 234, Folder 29)
    - Beauty Part: New York "closed", Nov 23, 1974 (Box 234, Folder 30)
    - Bread: New York "closed", Feb 9, 1974 (Box 234, Folder 31)
    - Cherry Tree Business: Westminster, Maryland, 1976 (Box 234, Folder 32)
    - Chickencoop Chinaman's Pregnant Pause: New York "closed", Jun 24, 1972 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Cold Storage: New York "closed", May 8, 1977 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Creeps: New York "closed", Dec 16, 1973 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - Decline and Fall of the Entire World According to Cole Porter: Chicago, Illinois, 1973-1974 (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Divorce of Judy and Jane: New York "closed", Apr 30, 1972 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - Fingernails Blue as Flowers and Lake of the Woods: New York "closed", Jan 8, 1972 (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Enemy is Dead: New York "closed", Jan 14, 1973 (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - Foreplay: New York "closed", Oct 10, 1971 (Box 235, Folder 8)
    - Freeman: New York "closed", Feb 24, 1973 (Box 235, Folder 9)
    - Gaughin: Chicago, Illinois, 1976 (Box 235, Folder 10)
    - Good Look at Boney Korn: Albuquerque, New Mexico "abandoned", 1977 (Box 235, Folder 11)
    - Good Look at Boney Korn: New Hope, Pennsylvania "closed", Jun 26, 1977 (Box 235, Folder 12)
    - Gorky: New York "closed", Nov 30, 1975 (Box 235, Folder 13)
    - Hamlet: School Tour New York "closed", Mar 16, 1973 (Box 235, Folder 14)
    - Hashish Club: New York "closed", Jan 11, 1975 (Box 235, Folder 15)
    - Haym Solomon the Liberty Broker: New York, 1975 (Box 235, Folder 16)
    - Hold Me: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania "closed" [also known as Jules Feiffer's Hold Me], Nov 6, 1977 (Box 235, Folder 17)
    - Hold Me: Washington, D.C. "closed" [includes correspondence re: 1977 New York production], Dec 11, 1977 (Box 235, Folder 18)
    - Hosanna: New York "closed", Nov 3, 1974 (Box 235, Folder 19)
    - House Party: New York "closed", Nov 24, 1973 (Box 235, Folder 20)
    - I Am A Woman: New York, 1974 (Box 235, Folder 21)
    - Ichabod: Boston, Massachusetts "closed", Apr 10, 1977 (Box 235, Folder 22)
    - Indian Experience: New York "closed", Oct 23, 1973 (Box 235, Folder 23)
    - Isadora Duncan Sleeps with the Russian Navy: New York "closed", Feb 20, 1977 (Box 235, Folder 24)
    - Jack Gelber's New Play: New York "closed", Oct 24, 1976 (Box 235, Folder 25)
    - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well and Living in Paris: New York "closed", Jul 2, 1972 (Box 235, Folder 26)
    - Julius Caesar: New York "abandoned" during rehearsals, May 5, 1975 (Box 235, Folder 27)
    - Kaboom: New York "closed", May 5, 1974 (Box 235, Folder 28)
    - Karl Marx Play: New York "closed", Apr 14, 1973 (Box 235, Folder 29)
    - Karl Marx Play: Tour (European) "closed", Nov 16, 1973 (Box 235, Folder 30)
    - Le Bellybutton: New York "closed", Apr 25, 1976 (Box 235, Folder 31)
    - Let My People Come: Never officially opened at the Village Gate in New York then "closed" [moved to Broadway], Jul 5, 1976 (Box 235, Folder 32)
    - Let My People Come: Washington, D.C. "closed", Mar 13, 1977 (Box 235, Folder 33)
    - Macbeth: New York "closed", Jun 23, 1976 (Box 235, Folder 34)
    - Man on the Moon: New York "closed", Feb 1, 1975 (Box 235, Folder 35)
    - Marriage-Go-Round: Pinehurst, North Carolina "closed", Jul 17, 1977 (Box 235, Folder 36)
    - Medea and Jason: New York "closed", Oct 24, 1974 (Box 235, Folder 37)
    - Metamorphosis: New York "closed", May 6, 1972 (Box 235, Folder 38)
    - Midsummer Night's Dream: New York "closed", Mar 16, 1975 (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Miracle Play: New York "closed", Jan 7, 1974 (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Molly: Spoleto Festival, Charleston, South Carolina "closed", Jun 5, 1977 (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - My Sister, My Sister: New York "closed", Aug 11, 1974 (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - National Lampoon Lemmings: New York "closed", Nov 18, 1973 (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Oh! Calcutta!: Eden Theatre New York "closed" [moved to Belasco Theatre on a full Production Contract], Feb 21, 1971 (Box 236, Folder 6)
    - Old Glory: New York "closed", May 23, 1976 (Box 236, Folder 7)
    - Old Glory: Tour (European) "closed", Jun 27, 1976 (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - Passing Game: New York "closed", Dec 11, 1977 (Box 236, Folder 9)
    - Plays the Thing: New York "closed", May 26, 1973 (Box 236, Folder 10)
    - P.S. Your Cat is Dead: Boston, Massachusetts "closed", Aug 13, 1977 (Box 236, Folder 11)
    - Quarter for the Ladies Room: New York "closed", Nov 18, 1972 (Box 236, Folder 12)
    - Richard III: New York "closed", Dec 22, 1974 (Box 236, Folder 13)
    - Ride the Wind: New York "closed", May 18, 1974 (Box 236, Folder 14)
    - Roots: New York "closed" [request to change to Off-Broadway contract denied], May 6, 1961 (Box 236, Folder 15)
    - Rubbers and Yanks 3, Detroit 0, Top of the Seventh: New York "closed", Sep 21, 1975 (Box 236, Folder 16)
    - Second Greatest Entertainer in the Whole Wide World: Boston, Massachusetts "closed", Jan 1, 1977 (Box 236, Folder 17)
    - Second Greatest Entertainer in the Whole Wide World: Boston, Massachusetts "closed", Feb 17, 1977 (Box 236, Folder 18)
    - Sextet: New York "closed", Mar 10, 1974 (Box 236, Folder 19)
    - Sexual Perversity in Chicago and Duck Variations(also known as The Mamet Plays) Washington, D.C. "closed", Jun 5, 1977 (Box 236, Folder 20)
    - Shortchanged Review: New York "closed", Feb 29, 1976 (Box 236, Folder 21)
    - Sleep: New York "closed", Mar 11, 1972 (Box 236, Folder 22)
    - Snoopy: San Francisco Company, 1976 (Box 236, Folder 23)
    - Straw in the Wind: New York "closed", Mar 22, 1975 (Box 236, Folder 24)
    - Taking of Miss Janie: New York "closed", Jun 15, 1975 (Box 236, Folder 25)
    - Tarot: New York "closed", Dec 20, 1970 (Box 236, Folder 26)
    - Tempest: New York "closed", Apr 7, 1974 (Box 236, Folder 27)
    - Troilus and Cressida: New York "closed", Dec 23, 1973 (Box 236, Folder 28)
    - Tubstrip: New York "closed", Nov 17, 1975 (Box 236, Folder 29)
    - Turkey Delight: New York, 1976 (Box 236, Folder 30)
    - Two by Five: New York, 1976 (Box 236, Folder 31)
    - Unexpected Guest: New York "closed", Mar 6, 1977 (Box 236, Folder 32)
    - Unfair to Goliath: New York "closed", Mar 29, 1970 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - Vanities: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania "closed", Feb 18, 1979 (Box 237, Folder 2)
    - Wheelbarrow Closers: New York "closed", Oct 16, 1976 (Box 237, Folder 3)
    - Year of the Dragon: New York "closed", Jun 15, 1974 (Box 237, Folder 4)
    - Your Arms Too Short to Box With God: Washington, D.C. "closed", [May 2, 1976] (Box 237, Folder 5)
  - Subseries I: Café Contract
    - El Grande de Coca Cola: Los Angeles, California, 1975 (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - El Grande de Coca Cola: Ocean Beach (Fire Island), New York, 1977 (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - In Gay Company: New York "closed", Feb 23, 1975 (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - In Gay Company: New York "closed", Apr 5, 1975 (Box 237, Folder 9)
    - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well and Living in Paris: Boston, Massachusetts "closed", Nov 24, 1974 (Box 237, Folder 10)
    - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well and Living in Paris: Cleveland, Ohio "closed", Jan 4, 1976 (Box 237, Folder 11)
    - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well and Living in Paris: Los Angeles, California "closed", [Sep 4, 1973] (Box 237, Folder 12)
    - Jacques Brel is Alive and Well and Living in Paris: Washington, D.C. "closed", Jun 17, 1973 (Box 237, Folder 13)
    - Look Me Up: New York "closed", May 21, 1972 (Box 237, Folder 14)
    - Love Song: Toronto, Ontario, Canada "closed", May 19, 1973 (Box 237, Folder 15)
    - Night Sounds: New York "closed", Apr 24, 1976 (Box 237, Folder 16)
    - Oh, Coward!: Cleveland, Ohio "closed", Dec 21, 1975 (Box 237, Folder 17)
    - Say When: New York "closed", Dec 8, 1972 (Box 237, Folder 18)
    - Second City: Chicago, Illinois contract, 1971, 1974 (Box 237, Folder 19)
    - Tubstrip: Washington, D.C. "closed", Jan 12, 1975 (Box 237, Folder 20)
    - Way It Is: New York "closed", Jan 20, 1970 (Box 237, Folder 21)
    - What's a Nice Country Like You Doing in a State Like This?: New York "closed", May 4, 1974 (Box 237, Folder 22)
    - What's a Nice Country Like You Doing in a State Like This?: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania "closed", Apr 12, 1975 (Box 237, Folder 23)
  - Subseries J: Letter Form of Agreement/Letter of Agreement
    - Actors' Alliance at the Provincetown Playhouse, New York City, 1976 (Box 237, Folder 24)
    - Greengate Theatre at Sarah Lawrence College, Bronxville, New York, 1977 (Box 237, Folder 25)
    - Off-Broadway Theatre in the Suburbs at the Henry Kagan Community House, Mt. Vernon, New York, 1974 (Box 237, Folder 26)
    - Hudson Guild Theatre, New York City, 1977-1978 (Box 237, Folder 27)
    - Hudson Guild Theatre, New York City: Exhibits requested for a meeting with the Showcase Code Committee (SCC), 1978 (Box 237, Folder 28)
    - Labor Theatre, New York City, 1976-1977 (Box 237, Folder 29)
    - Manhattan Theatre Club, New York City, 1976 (Box 237, Folder 30)
    - Manhattan Theatre Club, New York City, 1977 (Box 237, Folder 31)
    - Musical Theatre Lab at the Kennedy Center, Washington, D.C. (includes some earlier material), 1977 (Box 237, Folder 32)
    - New Stages, II, Newport, Rhode Island, 1977 (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Playhouse at Piccadilly Square, Newton, Massachusetts, 1977 (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Playwrights Horizons for Queens Theatre in the Park, Flushing, New York, 1976-1977 (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Street Theater, New York City, 1976 (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - Westchester Rockland Regional Theatre, Harrison, New York, 1975-1977 (Box 238, Folder 5)
  - Subseries K: Summer Festival Contract
    - Othello: Shakespeare Summer Festival, Washington, D.C. "closed", Aug 18, 1973 (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - School for Wives: Phoenix Summer Festival, Trinity Square Repertory Company, Providence, Rhode Island "closed", Jun 18, 1972 (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - Taming of the Shrew: Shakespeare Summer Festival, Washington, D.C. "closed", Aug 7, 1975 (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - Tempest: Shakespeare Summer Festival, Washington, D.C. "closed", Aug 8, 1976 (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - Troilus and Cressida: Shakespeare Summer Festival, Washington, D.C. "closed", Aug 17, 1972 (Box 238, Folder 10)
    - Twelfth Night: Shakespeare Summer Festival, Washington, D.C. "closed", Aug 10, 1974 (Box 238, Folder 11)
    - Way of Thangs: Youth Board Research Institute, New York City "closed", Aug 29, 1971 (Box 238, Folder 12)
    - Winterset: Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre Company "closed", Aug 25, 1968 (Box 238, Folder 13)
    - Your Own Thing: Shakespeare Summer Festival, Washington, D.C. "closed", Aug 15, 1971 (Box 238, Folder 14)
  - Subseries L: Other
    - Agreement for this venue only: Ensemble Studio Theatre at Johnson State College, Johnson, Vermont, 1973 (Box 238, Folder 15)
    - Agreement for this venue only: Small's Paradise, New York City, 1958 (Box 238, Folder 16)
    - Backer's Audition Code: April's Fool, 1973 (Box 238, Folder 17)
    - Backer's Audition Code: Hello, Hello, Hollywood!, 1976 (Box 238, Folder 18)
    - Backer's Audition Code: Mrs. Carrie B. Phillips, 1971 (Box 238, Folder 19)
    - Backer's Audition Code: Oh, Lady! Lady!, 1975 (Box 238, Folder 20)
    - Backer's Audition Code: Robert and Elizabeth, 1970-1973 (Box 238, Folder 21)
    - Backer's Audition Code: Roberta, 1975 (Box 238, Folder 22)
    - Backer's Audition Code: A Strawberry Grew on an Apple Tree, 1971 (Box 238, Folder 23)
    - Backer's Audition Code: True to All Seven, 1971 (Box 238, Folder 24)
    - Backer's Audition Code: Upstream, 1972 (Box 238, Folder 25)
    - Backer's Audition Code: "The Zimmer Girls" in Summer by the Sea, 1977 (Box 238, Folder 26)
    - Canadian Contract: National Ballet of Canada, 1974 (Box 238, Folder 27)
    - Canadian Contract: Playhouse Theatre Company, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1971 (Box 238, Folder 28)
    - Canadian Contract: Vancouver Festival (with correspondence to 1971), 1968 (Box 238, Folder 29)
    - Hollywood Area Theatre/Bay Area Theatre (HAT/BAT) Contract: Hold Me, San Francisco, California, 1977 (Box 238, Folder 30)